(3rd Selection,
Final Assignment, Tryouts)
I will now announce the teams.
I chose Team A.
And we'll be up against Team B.
1st Match
Who will I play alongside?
Who will I play against?
We only get one match.
For us total nobodies,
this is our final ticket...
(1st Match, Time Left Until Kickoff)
to becoming someone.
(Episode 26
The Assassin and the Ninja)
(Five Matches in Total)
There will be five matches in total.
And between each match,
there will be a six-hour interval.
To ensure fairness, observing
the other teams' matches is prohibited.
(You may not enter the arena)
You are not allowed to watch the other matches.
(You may not use the monitor room)
The first match will be Team A vs Team B.
Three players from each team
will be chosen at random.
Team A's first player is:
(Nanase)
Nanase Nijiro.
Yes, sir!
Their second player is:
(Hiori Yo)
Hiori Yo.
It's me, huh?
And their third player is...
Oh?
(Isagi)
Isagi Yoichi!
R-Right!
He flinched.
Right off the bat? The very first game?
(Team A's players)
I will now announce Team B's players.
(To Announce Team B's players)
Who are we up against?
(Shiguma)
Their first player is: Shiguma Kyohei.
Their second player is: Saramadara Kairu.
Man, they're both big guys.
A golem and a Predator, huh?
And their third player is...
(Chigiri)
Chigiri Hyoma.
'Kay.
Chigiri? That's a tough one for me.
Familiar foes, huh?
Both teams, please put on these shirts
and head to your respective gates.
I have to focus on displaying
my presence in this team.
In these tryouts,
even my teammates are my rivals.
I'm so fricking buzzed.
"Buzzed"?
If we play well here, we become the U-20.
It's finally our time to shine.
Ah, my bad, my guy. Back where I'm from,
"buzzed" means, like, "excited."
I'm Nanase, bro. I'm a first-year.
Oh, uh, I'm Isagi. Nice to meet you.
I'm a second-year.
So that makes ya my senior!
I'm all prepared to let ya teach me stuff!
S-Sure thing.
I'm also a second-year.
Name's Hiori. Nice to meetcha.
Oh, that's a Kansai accent.
Yeah, I'm from Kyoto.
Hey, so if you are a Kyotoite,
that doesn't make ya an elephant?
Do you mean "elegant"?
So I'm an elephant now, am I?
My bad, my guy.
Shucks.
Wait, what is this sense of unity?
It's so refreshing!
Lock off.
Donkey.
I'll kill you.
(BLEAK)
It's been unrelentingly bleak so far.
The one-two passing I was doing...
He copied it after seeing it once?
Hiori's passing is incredible.
Try to outrun me,
Mr. Genius's Little Bro.
Too slow.
Gimme it, No.1.
Back off, Antenna Boy.
I'm gonna stop you!
What?
Huh?
Using Shidou's movement as a decoy,
he waited until the goalie's view was
obstructed before hitting a "blind" shot.
Nice.
Hah. So Itoshi Rin really
is on a whole other level.
It's no good.
I can't get into this game at all.
I'm getting pinned down
by Karasu individually,
and Rin and Shidou are having
no problems scoring without me.
At this rate, the game will end
without me doing anything.
I need to shake off Karasu and wheedle
my way into their attacking patterns.
How can I show my presence in this game?
I'm sure that's what Isagi's thinking,
but the truth is,
aside from the four Top 6 players,
no one's managed to assert themselves
in this match, myself included.
For the Top 6, we're nothing
but replaceable pawns.
But if I try to force things, I'll just end up
spinning my wheels and making myself bait.
Don't go competing with No.1.
Shut up. I'll do what I want.
Then, I ain't passing to ya, dumdum.
Never asked you to.
I won't worry about the situation right now.
I'll just focus on what
I can do in the moment!
Come and get it, No. 2.
Even if I try to get in between them,
he won't pass to me
unless I'm more agile than Otoya.
So if I wanna survive, I shouldn't hang about
the center of the field where it's congested,
but go out to the right wing!
My legs can kick it into high gear and reach
top speed when I've got space to run into.
I don't need to adjust to their attacks!
I'll...
I'll pry open this field with my own weapon!
I'll blast it!
Even if I have to bundle him over...
Look at me, Karasu!
...I'll stop him!
Don't you wanna use these legs?!
Not bad, Red.
I'll give you a chance.
Karasu?
It got to me!
Not so fast, redhead.
Perfection, ninja dude.
Right now, this is the only option, isn't it?!
Your speed...
gets me real excited.
Hell yeah!
Chigiri...
He showed them a new possibility for their
attack pattern and made them acknowledge him.
Nice cross, lady ninja.
I'm a guy, you know.
This one's useful.
So that's "assertion and coexistence."
For those of us outside of the Top 6,
that's the only way to survive.
Damn it. Rin's not even
considering using me.
Hiori?
While assessing the situation,
he's calmly passing it around with Rin.
He's desperate to get involved
in the game by doing what he can.
In that case, I'll do what I can do.
I'll position myself in front of the goal
and wait for a chance to hit my direct shot!
Oh no you don't, Mr. Average.
Karasu?
I'll run into his blind spot off-the-ball!
Ya thought I wouldn't see that?
Damn it all! I'm not done yet!
In front of the goal? Right there?
Here it comes! The perfect trajectory.
No, wait. It's another pass to Rin?
Nope. It's for me.
You...
Shidou?
The hell are youse doin'?
Got it! Push up!
Let's counter, Otoya!
A short ball to Karasu.
There's no straight man in your double act?
Then, allow me to deliver the punch line.
Aw, hell. They're close to winning.
This is bad.
But why'd they crash into each other?
Rin reads the field and arrives
at the optimal course of action,
while Shidou relies on instinct
to pick the perfect choice.
They got the same answer, but couldn't link up
because their processes were so different?
That was mine!
Antenna berserker!
Irritating bottom eyelash jerk!
Is it possible these two Top 6 players
have the worst compatibility?
No, wait.
Is this a piece I can take advantage of?
Blue Lock Additional Time!
(Blue Lock Additional Time!)
(Isagi Yoichi
Episode 26: Each Parallel World)
(Thunk)
Man, I'm starving.
But I need something to drink now.
Hm, water or tea?
Oh, while I'm here, I'll get some
for Nanase and Hiori, too.
Huh?
(Hiori Yo) (Nanase Nijiro) (Huh)
Oh?
Huh?
Were we all thinking the same thing?
Yup.
Silly us.
(Gentle Parallel World)
Behold, the gentle parallel world!
(Shiguma Kyohei, Chigiri Hyoma)
We're only together for one match,
(Saramadara Kairu)
but it's nice working with you.
In battle, the one who finds
the flow is the one who wins.
I'm a surfer, and finding the flow
is how I've survived so far.
Jeez, Predatorhead's
going off about something.
How about the golem over here?
Nice working with you.
I shouldn't talk to suspicious people.
That's what Gram-gram told me.
He's just a rude grandma's boy!
I'm gonna be the big wave.
These guys are impossible.
(Incompatible Parallel World)
Behold, the incompatible parallel world.
(Aryu Jyubei)
It's Itoshi Rin's Team A that can
create chemical reactions with my glam.
That's the most glam choice.
And...
If the other two alongside me are also glam,
(Team Super Glam)
I can shine and show off as Team Super Glam.
This presence is...
Tanaka Shingen.
(Tanaka Shingen)
Gotta take a whiz.
So crude. So not glam.
(Wanima Junichi)
Wanima Junichi.
(Pluck!)
Glare!
Care complete.
(Pluck!)
His idea of beauty is so not glam.
(Igarashi Gurimu)
Igarashi Gurimu.
Namusan soccer!
Just as a life form, he is so not glam.
God, please don't make me team up
with these three totally un-glam rubes.
(So-Not-Glam Parallel World)
Hey, look! A giant booger!
I-It's huge!
Namu ami-double up!